噢  托比
Oh, Toby.
我觉着你是我最可爱的孩子
I think you're my cutest baby yet.
嘿
Hey.
噢
Oh.
我最可爱的儿子
My cutest boy baby.
嘿
Hey.
噢
Oh.
噢  我感觉咱家最可爱的儿子
Oh, I think cutest boy baby.
吐奶了
Just had a little spit up.
噢  奶哥去哪了
Oh. where's my "up man"?
奶哥
Up man!
奶哥是什么
What's an up man?
不知道吗  他处理各种婴儿问题
You know, he takes care of the "ups."
吐奶啊  打扫啊  呕吐啊
Spit-up, clean-up, throw-up.
在呢
I'm here.
谢谢
Thank you.
为什么让我当奶哥
Why do I have to be the up man?
因为你
Because you...
因为啥事要惩罚他来着
Why is it we're punishing him again?
这个  因为他
Well, because he...
他是盖比
He's Gabe.
我们了解他的所作所为
We know he did something.
-没错  -是啊
-Yep. -Yeah.
也许吧
Probably.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第八集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E08  Welcome Home
看啊  看看这里
Well, lookie here.
这牛奶明天就过期了
This milk expires tomorrow.
哼
Huh.
说到明天  挺
Speaking of tomorrow, pretty...
挺特殊的啊  哼
Pretty special day, huh?
明天肯定没有人
It won't be for anyone.
想喝掉这牛奶
Who drinks that milk.
当然不是  傻瓜
No, silly.
明天就十个月了
Tomorrow is 10 months.
十个月
10 months?
自从我们
Since we...
自从我们和好啊
Since we got back together.
明天是我们的十个月纪念日啊
Tomorrow is our 10-month-aversary.
没错  我刚才是逗你玩呢
Right, no. I'm just messing with you.
明天晚上  我
Tomorrow night, I'm...
带你去个有情调的地方共进晚宴
Taking you out to a special fancy dinner.
你真的没忘吗
So you really remembered?
当然没忘  没忘  没忘
Yeah, no. of course. of cou...
-看看我的日历  -恩
-Check out my calendar. -Hmm.
我还特意将明天的日期用心形标注了一下
Tomorrow's date has a heart on it.
让我看看
Let me see.
等等
Hang on.
好了  给你
All right, here we go.
看
See?
那是小狗
And that's a puppy.
等等  等等
Hang on. hang on.
天啊  有了大家共同的帮助
Gosh, with everyone helping out,
托比在家的第一周
Toby's first week at home has been.
真的是很美妙
Absolutely wonderful.
惊喜
Surprise!
-妈  -奶奶
-Mom! -Grandma.
-嘿  -嗷
-Hey. -Aww.
-好啊  -嗨
-Hello. -Hi.
这周会变得越来越美妙
And the week just keeps getting better.
您怎么来了
What are you doing here?
还带着行李箱
With your suitcase?
噢  如果我不过来看看我的小孙子什么的
Oh! what kind of a grandmother would i be.
那我还算什么奶奶
If i didn't come to see my new grandson and whatnot?
妈啊  你真好
Mom, you're the best.
噢   谢谢了  阿鲍
Oh, thank you, honey.
你看起来也不错
You look wonderful.
艾米啊  你还是穿着
And Amy, you're still wearing.
那件衣服
That same outfit.
我真是看不够啊
I never get tired of seeing it.
我喜欢礼物
I like presents.
噢
Oh.
我没忘
I remembered that.
想看看袋子里有什么吗
Do you want to look in the bag?
我喜欢现金
I like cash.
我手头不富裕
I'm on a fixed income.
艾米  我不是来这里度假的
Amy, I'm not here on vacation.
我来这里是帮助做家务什么的
I'm here to help out with the chores and whatnot.
不闲聊了  我想看看我的托比
No more chitchat. I want to see my toby.
噢  天啊
Oh, my.
你真是个帅小伙啊  托比
What a handsome boy you are, toby.
长得真像电影明星啊
Are you gonna look like a movie star,
就像你爸爸那样
Just like your daddy?
她上次去电影院是哪年的事情了
When was the last time she went to a movie?
噢  嘿 达布尼夫人
Oh, hey, Mrs. dabney.
嗯
Hmm...
看来今天是老太太光顾邓肯家日
Guess it's old lady day here at the duncan house.
给你们的
This is for you.
我在阁楼找到了些以前的婴儿用品
It's some old baby stuff i found in my attic.
我的意思是  只要你爹妈
I mean, as long as you people.
每五分钟生一个  这些都算以前的婴儿用品
Keep having babies every five minutes.
噢  看看这个拨浪鼓
Oh. check out this old rattle.
那是我儿子罗德尼的
That was my son Rodney's.
他可喜欢这东西了
He loved that thing.
这种有节奏的声音
The rhythmic noise.
能催眠他的神经
Would just mesmerize his little mind.
PJ
PJ.
嗯
Hmm?
噢  嗨  达布尼夫人
Oh, hi, Mrs. Dabney.
知道吗  这里面可能会有些
You know, there might be some things here.
能让你哥俩感兴趣的东西
That you boys would be interested in.
我们不要你的老古董垃圾
We don't want your old junk.
好吧
Fine.
那我就把这些漫画书扔掉
I'll just throw these old comics.
然后再扔棒球卡
And baseball cards away then.
别  别  别  我的意思是
No, no, no! I mean...
我们就勉为其难的收下了  你欠我们个人情
We'll take them, but you owe us.
现在  一天之中最精彩的部分来了
And now, the best part of my day...
撤退
Leaving.
别弄了
Stop that.
噢  嘿  盖比
Oh, hey, Gabe.
嗨  宝贝
Hi, honey.
嘿  什么事
Hey, what's going on?
噢  没什么事
Oh, nothing much.
无关紧要
This and that.
噢  有一件小事
Oh, there was one more little thing.
什么来着  什么来着  什么来着
What was it, what was it, what was it?
噢  想起来了  我受不了你奶奶
Oh, yeah. I can't stand grandma.
但她是世界上最可爱的女士了
But she's the sweetest lady in the world.
不  不  不  不
No, no. no. no.
她是世界上最可爱的女士
She's the sweetest lady in the world.
什么的
And whatnot.
是啊  她的确老这么说
Yeah, she does say that a lot,
是不是
Doesn't she?
不仅是这个
It's not just that.
还有声音啊  微笑啊  聊天啊
It's the voice, and smile, and the comments,
还有“阿鲍是个电影明星”
And the "bobby's a movie star."
拜托  如果咱家里有电影明星
Please. if anyone's around here's a movie star,
那也是我
It's me.
好了  老妈
Well, mom,
她也就是来咱家住两天
She's only going to be here for two more days.
你就不能忍忍吗
Can't you just get through it?
不知道
I don't know.
生完宝宝之后  荷尔蒙还未消退
After the baby, I'm all hormonal,
就是
Just...
没有了自控能力
I don't have my usual censor.
你有自控能力
You have a censor?
泰迪  你要救救老娘我啊  好不
Teddy, you have to help me, okay?
你要让奶奶远离我
You gotta keep grandma away from me.
好吧  好吧  我  我喜欢
Yeah, sure. I... I love spending time.
和奶奶在一起
With grandma.
以防外一她踩到我的神经
And just in case she gets on my nerves,
我们需要个暗号
We need a code word.
知道吗  想出某种暗号
You know, something I can say.
防止我气炸了
In case I'm about to blow.
鸭嘴兽兽  这个词有意思
Platypi. that's a fun word.
是鸭嘴兽的复数
It's the plural for platypus.
噢  亲爱的
Oh, honey.
我需要某种能出现在正常谈话中的词
I need something that I can work into a conversation.
呃
Um...
苹果
Apple.
我在动物园看见了两只鸭嘴兽
I was at the zoo and I saw two platypi.
不错吧
How easy is that?
还是苹果吧
We'll go with apple.
破玩意
Meh.
不要
No.
噢  嘿
Oh. hey.
看看这老古董漫画书
Check out this old comic book.
“蜥蜴怪物人”
"Gila Monster Man."
蜥蜴怪物人  讲的是啥
Gila monster man? what's that about?
“白天  他是个为人谦逊的摄影师  吉尔 A·明斯特”
"By day, he's mild mannered photographer, Gil A. Muenster."
到了晚上  他是个惩恶扬善的超级英雄
By night, he's a crime-fighting superhero.
“蜥蜴怪兽人”
"Gila monster man."
好吧  他的超能力是什么
All right, what's his super power?
“当他躲在热岩石下时”
"When he hides under hot rocks,"
他的体温迅速升高
His body temperature rises.
“可以将敌人迅速烧焦”
"And gives him the ability to scorch villains."
我可不愿意成为爱看这种东西的呆子
I'd hate to be the geek with that lunch box.
是不是啊
You know?
-什么东西  -以前的信
-What's that? -Just some old letter.
嘿  上面写着1924年7月9日
Hey, it's dated july 9, 1924.
-哇  -听着
-Wow. -Listen to this.
“亲爱的兄弟”
"My dearest brother,"
当我病危之时
As I am very ill,
我将寄给你一封非常紧急的信件
I send you this letter with great urgency.
正如你所知  尽管我腰缠万贯
As you know, in spite of my great wealth,
“但是我被银行列入了不信赖黑名单”
"I have had a lifelong distrust of banks."
蜥蜴怪兽人在冬天怎么办
What does gila monster man do during the winter?
安静  安静  安静
Quiet, quiet, quiet.
此处省略一万字
Blah, blah, blah, blah...
“我所有的钱财都埋在了我家的后院里”
"All my money is buried in the backyard of my home,"
就在橡树正东十英尺处
10 feet due east from the oak tree,
四英尺深
And four feet deep.
“此致敬礼  你的兄弟  奥维尔”
"With loving regard, your brother, Orville."
等一下  看看这个
Wait a minute, look at this.
他住在达布尼夫人家里
He lived in mrs. Dabney's house.
而且这封信从未寄出去
And the letter was never mailed.
咱俩想到一起了吗
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
我们要去趟邮局
We gotta get to the post office.
PJ  这封信从未寄出过
PJ, the letter was never mailed.
没有人知道钱的事情
No one knows about the money.
很有可能还在那里
It's probably still there.
所以等到达布尼夫人走后
So when mrs. Dabney's gone,
我们把钱挖出来
We go dig it up.
噢
Oh.
我们就发财了
And we're rich.
没错  那是当然了  君子的做法就是
Well, of course, the right thing to do.
我们把钱和达布尼夫人均摊
Would be to split it evenly with mrs. Dabney.
我们要小人了  是不是
We're gonna do the wrong thing, though, aren't we?
往后挪
Move it back.
就在那
There.
现在  感觉好多了吧  阿鲍
Now, isn't that better, bobby?
是好多了  老妈
It is better, mommy.
嗨
Hi.
发生了什么
What's going on?
噢  就是重置了下家具什么的
Oh, just a little rearranging and whatnot.
噢
Oh.
这么做好吗
Is that a good idea?
噢  当然了
Oh, yes.
这是中国古代艺术
It's an ancient chinese art.
叫做“风水”
It's called "fung shooey."
嘿  亲  进来一下
Hey, hon. come on in here a second.
哼
Huh?
感觉怎么样
What do you think?
很好
Love it.
这样更容易打扫
It's easier to clean this way.
我知道这一向都对你有些挑战
I know that's always been a challenge for you.
苹果
Apple.
什么
What?
老妈估计是在商量
Mom's probably just talking about.
我们今天晚上吃什么
What we're gonna have for dinner tonight.
苹果吗
Apple?
你不觉着晚饭应该
Don't you think we need something.
弄丰盛一点吗
A little more filling?
苹果
Apple.
奶奶  你还没参观我的房间呢
Grandma, you haven't seen my room.
来看看我的房间
Come see my room.
好的
Okay.
那么  我们吃焦糖苹果吗
So, like a caramel apple?
谢谢带我参观你的房间  宝贝
Thanks for the tour of your room, sweetheart.
真是尽收眼底
It was certainly through.
噢  别走  等等
Oh, no. uh, wait.
呃
Um...
咱们干点事情
Let's do something.
只有你和我
You know, just you and me.
我需要奶奶多陪陪我
I need some more grandma time.
好吧
All righty.
我不敢肯定你会很享受
I'm not sure you're going to enjoy it,
但我有个主意也许会很有趣
But I have an idea that might be fun.
折价券达人
Extreme couponing.
Extreme couponing?
没错  让我解释一下游戏规则
Well, let me explain how it works.
现在这个值五十美分
Now this one's worth 50 cents,
但她是双重折扣
But it's a double coupon.
也就是说它值一美元
Which means it's actually worth a dollar.
厉害
Cool!
如果我将它使用在特殊商品上
If I use this one on a qualifying item,
它就是三倍的双重折扣
It's triple times the double.
不管你信不信  我上次花了十二美分买到了
Believe it or not, I once got a case of pickle relish.
一份酸黄瓜
For 12 cents.
怎么样
How was it?
一般  我不是很爱吃酸黄瓜
Well, I'm not a pickle person.
呃
Um...
“买一包五磅重的猫砂
"Buy one 5-pound bag of kitty litter,
再买第二包可免费”
Get the second bag free."
别忘了让你的双重折扣翻三倍
Don't forget to triple your double.
这个太牛了
This is awesome.
知道吗  我们没有猫
You know, we don't have a cat,
如果我们养了  我们会让它免费随地大小便的
But if we did, he'd be pooping for free.
嘘  嘘
Shh. shh.
你俩
Guys...
我知道我会后悔问你们的  但是
I know I'm going to regret asking this, but...
你俩准备拿这些东西去哪啊
Where are you going with that stuff?
-图书馆  -我们在演戏
-The library. -We're in a play.
呃
Uh...
我们要在图书馆里演戏
We're in a play at the library.
什么戏啊
And what is the name of the play?
“铁铲
"Shovel...
少年”
Kids."
是关于背着铲子的少年
It's about kids who carry around shovels...
嘲笑那些
And make fun of the kids.
背着鹤嘴锄的孩子
Who carry around pickaxes.
噗  哈  傻子
Pfft. ha. dork.
你不应该取笑拿着鹤嘴锄
You should never make fun of someone.
的孩子
With a pickax.
这句是我的台词
That's one of my lines.
好了
Okay.
你在干嘛
What you doing?
噢  只是想搞清事实
Oh, want to get my facts straight...
碰一碰运气
Just on the off chance
我一会要去填写一份警方报告
I have to fill out a police report later on.
噢  玩了五个小时的优惠券
Oh, five hours of couponing...
真是尽兴啊
That was quite a sesh.
奶奶  我现在满眼都是虚线正常吗
Grandma, is it normal to see dotted lines.
看哪都是
Everywhere you look?
我要上楼了
I'm gonna head upstairs.
噢  别  呃
Oh, no, um,
咱们再找点别的乐趣吧
Let's do something else fun.
噢  但你老妈估计会需要我的帮助
Oh, but your mother probably needs my help.
什么的
And whatnot.
但我这里也需要你的帮助啊
But I need your help down here.
什么啊
With what?
那个  呃
With, um...
呃  那个
Uh... with...
化妆
A makeover.
你想让我给你化妆吗
You want me to give you a makeover?
是啊  知道吗
Yeah, I mean, you know,
我  我对现在的形象有点儿腻了
I've... I've been feeling kind of bored with my look.
而且你的品位又这么高
And you have such a great sense of style.
此话不假  我还真另外带了一罐发胶
Well, I did pack an extra can of hair spray.
噢  完了
Oh, no.
老鲍  亲爱的  你不是电影明星
Bob, honey. you're not a movie star.
我给你们看点东西
I've got something to show you.
请允许我向你们介绍全新的
May I present the new,
升级版  泰迪·邓肯
And improved, Teddy Duncan.
泰迪  你这是怎么了
Teddy, what happened?
噢  呃
Oh, um...
奶奶给我化妆了
Grandma gave me a makeover.
这样我们就能多陪陪对方
So we could spend more time together.
什么的
And whatnot.
还有更精彩的
And that's not all.
来吧  宝贝
Come on, sweetie.
来啊
Come on.
来  噢
Let's go. oh!
我的头发好硬
My hair is hard.
您好  女士
Hello, ma'am.
噢
Oh!
完了  今天是我们的十月周年晚宴
No. today is our 10-month-aversary dinner.
我忘得一干二净
I totally forgot.
是啊  当你上了年纪
Well, when you get older...
这位帅小伙是谁啊
Who's this handsome fellow?
噢  奶奶  这是我男朋友斯宾塞
Oh, grandma, this is my boyfriend Spencer.
斯宾塞  这是我奶奶琳达
Spencer, this is grandma Linda.
-你好  -嗨
-Hello. -Hi.
见到您很高兴
Nice to meet you.
你们一家子长得很像啊
I can see the family resemblance.
好了  我去换好行头
All righty. well, let me just go change real quick.
你换什么行头啊
Why do you need to change?
我们不是刚弄好吗
We just got you fixed up.
是啊  弄好了  呃
Yes, we did. um...
那我们就出发吧
I guess we're ready to go then.
噢  知道吗  我也要走了
Oh. you know what? I gotta go, too.
今晚要去打保龄球
It's bowling night.
这么一来
So...
泰迪去吃晚餐
Teddy's going to dinner,
你去打保龄球
And you're going bowling?
儿子们呢
Where are the boys?
呃  他们可能在图书馆呢
Uh. they might be at the library,
但是我不信
But I doubt it.
好了  琳达
Well, Linda...
看来今晚只剩咱俩了
Looks like it's just you and me tonight.
苹果
Apple?
或者
Or...
纪念日快乐
Happy anniversary.
知道吗
You know,
如果想挖快点
This would go a lot faster.
你也来帮忙
If you helped me dig.
PJ  在所有的合作关系中
PJ, in every partnership,
总会有劳动者和老板
There's labor and there's management.
-为什么我是劳动者  -因为我是老板
-Why am I labor? -Because I'm management.
等一下  停
Wait, stop.
我好像听见达布尼夫人停车呢
I think I just heard mrs. Dabney pull up.
-快跑  -好的
-Come on! -All right.
-快点  快点  -别催我  我已经不那么年轻了
-Hurry up, Hurry up. -Don't rush me. I'm not 12 anymore.
给您
Here you go.
这是给你们的  女士们
And for you, ladies,
老年菜单
The senior menu.
呃  能给我一份
Um, could I have.
正常的菜单吗  我  我才十七岁
A regular menu? I'm... I'm 17.
人老心不老啊
What a great attitude!
你们俩个能邀请我真是太好了
It's sweet of you kids to invite me,
但我感觉自己是个电灯泡
But I feel like I'm in the way.
噢  别这么想  我希望你在这里  奶奶
Oh, no. of course I want you here, grandma.
我有了称心的男友
I've got my favorite guy,
了不起的奶奶
My awesome grandma,
我的新形象
My great new look...
真是好事碰到一起了  对吧  斯宾塞
It's all coming together, right, Spencer?
那是当然了
You bet.
特别是因为你们二位的晚餐
Especially since both of your meals.
都半价
Will be half off.
噢  这倒提醒我了
Oh, which reminds me,
我把优惠券落车里了
I left my coupon in the car.
稍等一下
Excuse me.
他也好这口儿
He's a couponer, too?
你一定要抱住他的大腿
You'd better hang on to him.
噢  对不起  我们没点牛奶啊
Oh, I'm sorry. we didn't order milk.
这个是七号桌的男士送的
They're from the gentlemen at table seven.
这里怎么了
What's going on here?
欣赏下我的新温水浴池
Just admiring my new hot tub.
我不得不说  谢谢你们两个
And may I say, thank you, boys.
你们挖的这个坑帮我省了不少钱
That hole you dug saved me a lot of money.
我们没为温水浴池而挖坑
We weren't digging the hole for a hot tub.
我们在挖金矿
There's a fortune down there.
你笑什么
Why are you laughing?
还有你为什么把温水浴池建在了金矿上面
And why would you put a hot tub over a fortune?
真是愚蠢之极
That's so stupid.
她玩咱俩
She tricked us.
她写的那封信
She wrote the letter.
-她写的  -我写的
-She did? -I did.
她知道我们会挖这个坑的
She knew we'd dig the hole.
就在她指定好的位置上
Exactly where she wanted it.
我们才愚蠢之极
We're the stupid ones.
-是吗  -是的
-We are? -You are.
奶奶呢
Where's grandma?
她去厕所很长时间了
She's been in the bathroom a long time.
噢  呃  打扰一下
Oh, um, excuse me.
你看见和我们坐在一起的女士了吗
Have you seen the woman who was sitting with us?
看见了  她刚打了一辆出租车
Yes. she just got into a cab.
想让你们两个
Something about wanting you guys.
能有点私人空间什么的
To have some private time and whatnot.
噢  不  她回家了
Oh, no. she's going home!
鸭嘴兽兽
Platypi!
啥
What?
鸭嘴兽兽
Platypi.
你喜欢这个新布局吗
Aren't you loving the new setup?
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
让所有的负能量
It takes all the negative energy.
赶出家门
And pushes it right through the door.
还有点儿
Not all of it.
我们明天再看看厨房的“风水”
We'll be "fung shooing" the kitchen tomorrow.
不  不  不  厨房没有问题
No, no, no. nothing's wrong with the kitchen.
没错
You're right.
饭菜不好吃
Can't blame the kitchen.
也不能怪厨房的风水不好
For what goes on in there.
嗨
Hi.
怎么了
What's going on?
苹果  苹果  苹果
Apple, apple, apple.
你为什么总说这句话
Why do you keep saying that?
噢  这是我俩之间的游戏
Oh, it's just this fun thing that we do.
她说那个  我就回答说“派  派  派”
She says that and then I answer back, "pie, pie, pie!"
-不对  -不对吗
-No. -No!
我受不了了
I can't do this anymore.
你受不了什么
You can't do what anymore?
这些
This!
笑得像个傻子
Smiling like a ninny.
当你把我逼疯的时候
While you drive me out of my mind.
我承认你笑起来像个傻子
Well, I agree, you do smile like a ninny.
但是我看不出我哪里有问题
But I can't see where it's my fault.
看  又来了
See? there it goes again.
知道吗  那些挖苦  聊天
You know, the little digs, and the comments,
风水  还有什么的
And the rearranging, and whatnot.
什么的  什么的  什么的
Whatnot, whatnot, whatnot!
那到底是个啥意思
What does that even mean?
我  我从不知道你是这样的感受
I... I never knew you felt this way.
因为我把它深埋心底
Well, 'cause I've been keeping it inside.
已经二十年了
For the last 20 years.
如今我说出来了
And now that I've said it,
感觉不是很好
I feel terrible.
对不起  琳达
I'm so sorry, Linda.
噢   我是个差劲的人
Oh, I'm a horrible person.
噢  不  不
Oh, no, no.
你不是个差劲的人
You're not a horrible person.
你人很好
You're a wonderful girl.
还碰巧嫁了个好人家
Who just happened to marry very, very well.
你给这个家带来了美妙的生活
And you've given this family a wonderful life.
阿鲍有幸能拥有你
Bobby's lucky to have you.
谢谢
Thank you.
知道吗  虽然刚才的话不太好听
You know, as hard as it was to hear,
但是我很欣赏你的诚实
I appreciate your honesty.
我很感激你对我的欣赏
And I appreciate your appreciation.
这是太好了
This is nice.
真是太妙了
This is good.
好吧  既然我们坦诚相待
Well, as long as we're being honest,
我也跟你分享一些事情
I have some things I'd like to share about you.
呃  不要了
Um. no.
咱们现在挺好的
I think we're good.
我觉着咱们今天的进展不错
I think we've made enough progress for today.
过来吧  女士们  让我们一起
Come on, ladies. let's bring it in.
拥抱一下
Family hug.
嘿  大家好  打完保龄球回来了
Hey, everybody. back from bowling.
好了  查莉  奶奶走了
Well, Charlie, grandma's gone home,
所有事情都回归正常了
And everything is back to normal.
哼
Huh.
看啊
Look at that...
我哪面都好看
I really don't have a bad side.
好吧  不是所有事情
Well, maybe not everything.
我来吧
I'll get it.
我能找PJ和盖比聊聊吗
May I speak to PJ and Gabe?
达布尼夫人
Mrs. Dabney.
你  你身上有点儿东西
You got a... you got a little something.
有人往我的浴池里撒了点儿食用色素
Someone put food coloring in my hot tub.
啊
Ah.
小子们  有人找
Boys, you have a visitor.
你最好希望你的哥哥们
You'd better wish your brothers.
好运吧  查莉
Some good luck, Charlie.
现在  继续我们的
And now, the continuing adventures of...
蜥蜴怪兽人
Gila monster man!
这是三明治吧  明斯特
That's some sandwich, eh, Muenster?
没有错  警长
Sure is, chief.
警长
Chief!
我听到了一条消息
I just got a scoop.
蝎子医生又抢劫了一家银行
Doctor scorpion's robbed another bank.
瞪眼妖怪
Great googly-moogly!
那个魔鬼
That fiend.
天啊  我愿意捏碎这只虫子
Boy, I'd love to squash that bug.
逞什么能
Like you could do anything.
你只是个温文尔雅的新闻摄影师
You're just mild-mannered news photographer.
吉尔 A·明斯特
Gil A. Muenster.
并非像蜥蜴怪兽人那样的超级英雄
Not a real hero like gila monster man.
好吧  被你说中了
Well, you've got me there.
等一下  你去哪里
Wait! where are you going?
去找热岩石
To find a hot rock!
我是说
I mean...
洗手间
The bathroom.
蜥蜴怪兽人
Gila monster man!
你是从哪里出现的
Where'd you come from?
没时间闲聊
No time to talk.
蝎子医生在逍遥法外
Doctor scorpion's on the loose.
侯思特  快啊  拍照片
Holster, quick, get a picture.
那个白痴去哪了
Where is that mumbling idiot?